question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as "
                        "additional computing power instead of batteries.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his "
                        "lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used "
                        "chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio&#039;s character hunts down the killer of his son.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
